netobjects.com 2014-06-25

# NetObjects Privacy Policy

**NetObjects Privacy Policy**   
The following is the privacy policy for the www.netobjects.com Site. In this policy, NetObjects Incorporated ("NetObjects") describes what personal information NetObjects collects on our site, how NetObjects uses it, and your options regarding information NetObjects may collect about you. Where more details are needed to explain our privacy practices as to a particular NetObjects product or service, we may post separate privacy notices to describe how a particular NetObjects product or service processes personal information which is accessible from the topic index to the right of this Policy and/or links to the same. NetObjects strives to adhere to U.S. privacy laws and internationally accepted privacy principles established by the European Union Data Protection Directive, and the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union Safe Harbor Privacy Principles and this Policy is registered and certified by the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor program to ensure that your personal information is protected adequately. Should you desire more information on the safe harbor principles, please go to www.export.gov/safeharbor. 

If you have questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at:

NetObjects Inc.  
99 Lantern Drive  
Suite 302  
Doylestown, PA 18901

 **NetObjects's Use of Cookies and E-mail**  
NetObjects collects cookies on our Web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and NetObjects uses this information only internally - to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. NetObjects does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our Web site, our product or service check-out process, and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may also change your cookie settings through preferences options in our products and/or services, where applicable. NetObjects never gives away information about our users. If you choose to e-mail us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, NetObjects will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. NetObjects will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties unless such disclosure is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Policy, by law or a policy or notice contained or associated with a specific NetObjects product or service. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact our webmaster. 

  **Volunteered Information and Use of Information**  
When you license or subscribe to a product or service or open an account or complete an online registration on our site, NetObjects collects personal information from you which may include:

name and email address; 

billing information, including credit card information and your shipping address; 

information concerning software programs downloaded, products and content licensed, accessed, or downloaded through NetObjects products or services;   
location information (such as zip code or postal code and country); 

computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); 

the IP Internet (IP) address and URL of the Web site that sent you to the NetObjects registration page;   
demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, software program and content preferences and personalization information); and 

whether you logged into or out of a NetObjects service, or changed your password or billing information.   
This information is collected on Web pages using encryption technology to help prevent any third party from intercepting the information. Your credit card information is only used for completing the transaction and is retained only as necessary for administration purposes. NetObjects uses the information provided by our customers to analyze product trends based on, for example, geographic and demographic factors. This analysis helps us improve the quality of our Web site and product and service mix. 

**Information Collected in Contests**  
If you enter one of our contests, the data we collect will be handled according to the rules of that particular contest and those rules may differ based on where you live. We provide a privacy policy specific to each contest that you should review prior to entering the contest.

  **Downloading Software**  
When you download a NetObjects product, NetObjects asks you to provide your e-mail address in order to guide you through the 30-day trial period of using the software. We do not verify the validity of the e-mail address. You may unsubscribe from the follow up e-mails by contacting our webmaster at any time.

  **NOTICE**  
NetObjects informs its customers what information it collects, how it is used, whether it may be temporarily transferred to others to provide the products or services requested and how to contact NetObjects with privacy inquiries. NetObjects provides a link to NetObjects's privacy notice on its sites, and in e-mails.

  **CHOICE**  
NetObjects offers customers and individuals who provide us information choices about receiving further communications from us; for example, our e-mail newsletters have a link to use to opt out of receiving future messages. NetObjects may ask individuals if they wish to participate in market research, and then contact them if they give us their permission. NetObjects does not contact customers or individuals for marketing purposes for those persons who have contacted NetObjects directly to opt out of our direct marketing programs.

  **TECHNOLOGY**  
NetObjects uses technology in order to better serve its customers and others. NetObjects informs customers or individuals when NetObjects use technologies that are privacy related. 

  **DATA INTEGRITY & ACCESS**  
NetObjects takes steps to make sure that the personal information NetObjects uses is correct. NetObjects provides customers and individuals with reasonable access to the personal information they may have provided us so that they can review and correct it, or ask us not to use it. For example, customers or individuals may obtain a copy of the data they have provided, or update their information by contacting NetObjects' webmaster.

  **SECURITY**  
NetObjects protects personal information under its control by industry standard security practices and measures, in order to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. NetObjects limits access to personal information to those who have a business need. NetObjects does not keep personal information any longer than necessary to meet the business purpose for which it was collected, though in some cases, legal or regulatory reasons require that personal information not be deleted. NetObjects shall use its best efforts to quickly work to remedy any vulnerabilities found in our or software and to alert our customers about any potentially dangerous vulnerabilities. 

  **DATA TRANSFER**  
NetObjects may transfer personal information to NetObjects databases in countries other than where it was provided. NetObjects' privacy program requires the same high level of security and protection of personal information in all geographies with procedures and contracts in place to help ensure this is so. Data may be temporarily transferred to a vendor or business partner to provide services for NetObjects, such as mailing information or processing credit card transactions. These vendors and business partners are required to protect and manage the personal information to the same high standards NetObjects uses, and they cannot use the information for purposes other than to provide the services NetObjects has requested. Also, NetObjects may disclose or transfer your personal information, including, without limitation, personal information regarding customers under 13, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) satisfy an applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable NetObjects' Terms of Use, License or Service Agreements; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to protect against imminent harm to rights, property or safety of NetObjects, its users, or the public at large as required or permitted by law. 

  **INFORMATION PRACTICES FOR CHILDREN**  
NetObjects does not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13. If in the future we choose to collect personal information from children, we will comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

  **NOTIFICATION OF POLICY CHANGES**  
If major content changes are made to NetObjects' Privacy Policy, NetObjects will outline and post the changes along with the new version on this NetObjects site.

  **LINKS**  
NetObjects may create links to the sites of other parties. Independently operated sites are not associated with NetObjects or authorized by us and may also have links leading to this NetObjects site. NetObjects cannot control any of these links and are not responsible for any content appearing on the sites linked to or from NetObjects' site, or for any personal information gathered at those independently operated sites. 

  **DATA NOT COLLECTED ON THIS SITE**  
Personal information that is not collected on the site is not generally subject to this Privacy Policy. 

  **NON-U.S. CUSTOMER INFORMATION**  
If you are a customer or individual who is logging on from outside the United States, the personal information you submit to NetObjects will be sent to and stored in servers in our U.S. headquarters. The personal information practices set out in this Privacy Policy apply to all NetObjects products, services, and customers worldwide. You have a right of access and to correct such data and/or personal information. To exercise these rights, or for other data privacy questions, please contact/send an email to support@netobjects.com. 

  **ENFORCEMENT**  
NetObjects regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or NetObjects' treatment of personal information by contacting us through this Site at support@netObjects.com or by writing to us at Customer Relations, c/o NetObjects Inc., 99 Lantern Drive Suite 302, Doylestown, PA 18901,  USA. When NetObjects receives a formal written complaint at this address, it is NetObjects' policy to contact the complaining party regarding his or her concerns. NetObjects will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved by NetObjects and an individual. 

  **NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE**  
NetObjects does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. NetObjects will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when NetObjects learns of any failure to comply with our Privacy Policy. NetObjects shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania and the United States to the extent applicable.   
Last Updated: 06/08/2011 07:00:52

© 2014 NetObjects Inc. All Rights Reserved.  
NetObjects, NetObjects Fusion, SiteStyles and The Web Needs You are registered trademarks and Changing the World of Web Design, The Smart Way to Build Websites and Build Great Sites are trademarks of NetObjects Inc.
